So you learned a lot about redux
Ento, voc aprender muito sobre a Rydex.
over the last lectures and modules. I emphasized that there are alternatives and I showed you some best
Nas ltimas palestras e mdulos, enfatizei que existem alternativas e mostrei-lhe algumas boas prticas
practices, good practices and ways to optimize your reducers and actions.
de boas prticas e formas de otimizar seus redutores e aes.
You learned how to run asynchronous code with action creators like this one, how to use the redux-thunk
Voc aprendeu a executar cdigo assncrono com criadores de ao, como este, como usar o middleware do redux
middleware to do that,
fonk para fazer isso.
you learned how to combine reducers and how to use the redux dev tools to get insights into your store
Voc aprendeu a combinar redutores e a usar d read X dev tools para obter informaes sobre sua loja e
and even travel back in time if you want to.
at mesmo viajar de volta no tempo, se voc quiser.
These are all useful tools and redux is an extremely powerful library you'll see in a lot of react
em muitos aplicativos de reao, agora tambm voltar para o Bergere mais ousado e aprimorado  um pouco mais.
applications. We'll now also go back to our burger builder and enhance this a bit more
Estas so todas ferramentas teis e relaxar  uma biblioteca extremamente poderosa que voc ver
by for example adding asynchronous code and in conjunction with redux, and chances are you'll also work
O BI, por exemplo, adicionando cdigo assncrono e em conjunto com redox e as chances so que voc tambm
with it in your next project.
ir trabalhar com ele no prximo projeto.
The basics of this module should have you well prepared.
O bsico deste mdulo deve ter voc bem preparado.